This week is crazy.
There are a lot of big banks in the world.
Only in 7 months, they have bought about 40 million billion of Bitcoin.
This is the fastest price of the year 4th year.
Not only big banks, they have also made a big deal.
They have to prove that they have been completely done.
It's a terrible thing for others.
100% of family offices had some crypto, right?
And they're getting more serious about that over time.
That's moving into the general kind of investing mainstream.
Trump may be able to take the president of the president of the president.
Elon Musk may be able to join Trump's big banks.
This week's news.
I'll tell you.
It's hard to not to expect.
The big big big big big banks to come here.
Got the whole crypto world going wild.
Bonnie the day, she's the queen of the game.
Stacking crypto like it's her claim the same.
If you want success, take a look away.
Hello, I'm Bonnie.
And you'll see.
He said that in the past year,
because of the few people in the middle of the year,
the news is that the US will be more clear,
and the US will be more clear.
So he said that the Bitcoin goal is 10 million,
and the Bitcoin goal is 6500 million.
Satoshi Act,
the group of the internationalist, Dennis,
he said that Trump will probably
in the Bitcoin party on the US,
he said that the Bitcoin will be able to make the Bitcoin
as a strategy of the储备.
He said that if the Bitcoin will be able to change,
other countries will follow the idea of the world.
So this news is a big news.
Trump's team until now
still hasn't done this.
He said that
he said that
Bitcoin's supply chain after the Bitcoin
was not good.
He said that it was a healthy change.
Bitcoin's from弱手 to强手,
and it's more信心.
It's been a new investment.
The Bitcoin's supply chain is very fast.
And you'll see you at the other.
And you'll see you at other.
!
接下来今年的第四季
外界预估买量可能会逐渐增加
为什么呢
可能的影响包括11月要来的美国总统大选
然后开始降息之后
很多资金可能会放在银行里面
拿到的利息太少
可能会开始分配一些进到风险资产
像是加密货币里面
或是FTX交易所现在要赔偿了
它的还款都会带来新的买盘
尤其是FTX它的赔款预计是
160亿美元
它会否再次流进币圈市场
备受关注
And you can also speak.
as a second year of the State Financialistist
Larry Fink is the most beautiful world of the internet
And you know what you think is that you know.
And you know.
He also has a beautiful market.
One second.
Larry Fink is talking about the internet
And you know.
I was a skeptic.
Yes.
And you know.
learned about it, and I came away saying, okay, you know, my opinion five years was wrong. Here's
my opinion. Say this is what I believe in today. I believe the opportunity today. I believe Bitcoin
is legitimate. I'm not trying to say there's not misuses like everything else, but it is a
legitimate financial instrument that allows you to have maybe uncorrelated, non-correlated type
of returns. I believe it is an instrument that you invest in when you're more frightened, though.
It is an instrument when you believe that countries are debasing their currency,
debasing their currency by excess deficits, and some countries are. I believe we have
countries where you're frightened of your everyday existence and have an opportunity to invest in
something that is outside your country's, you know, control. Then you can have more financial control.
And so I'm a major believer that there is a role for Bitcoin in portfolios. I believe you're going
to see that as one of the asset classes that we all look at. I look at it as digital gold, as I said
before. And I do believe there's a real need for everyone to look at it as one alternative to,
I would say the optimism that I have in the world. If you want to hedge hope, Bitcoin is not an instrument for hope,
unless you're hopeful you're going to make a lot of money on it. But I look at it as a vehicle in which you're expressing your financial acumen in something that you're more frightened of the world,
you're more frightened of your existence. And I believe there's a great industrial use for it. And I think a lot of people are missing that.
And you'll see you.
And you can also tell you that you became aist.
And also,
He also became aist
Elon Musk
And the other thing is,
And the other thing is.
And also the other thing.
And the other thing.
And 2017.
And other things you can also encourage
is that
just that
the year
is still waiting to get down
to be延後
Trump even said
he thought
he should not get down
he said
like
技術自由
隐私
保護
these
are more
值得
we
to
find
he
He also wanted you to explore these other questions
He wanted you to explore these other questions
The SEC is
!
The
.
Only other e verte verte verte verte verte
at least have been
at the A.N.N.C.B.O.E.
other other other other other
other other other other
other other other
other other
large market
will also release
you.
More money into cryptocurrency
and blockchain
is not a rising tide
that lifts all boats. I believe we will see investment markets behave in relatively similar
ways. And what I mean by this is, let me give an example from the world of precious metals.
Gold is $14 trillion, $13 to $14 trillion in market cap. That is more than 10 times larger
than the next largest precious metal, right? And when investors want to go into precious metals
as a hedge for inflation, for example, they buy gold. They don't buy generally palladium or silver
or any other sort of specialized precious metal. I think we will see the same kind of behavior
in cryptocurrency. Bitcoin is digital gold. It will behave like digital gold. And I think it will
be as dominant to other crypto assets as gold is to other precious metals. Similarly, Ethereum has
become the dominant kind of tokenized asset and smart contract platform. I think there'll be kind
a similar effect there where Ethereum will soak up more than 90% of all these tokenized real
gold assets that companies like BlackRock and others are talking about deploying.
From the top of the ETF, James said that all the 10-day Ethereum ETFs will be released in
the 7-23th of the month.
Now, according to Citi Research out last Friday, Spot Ether ETFs could see net inflows of up to
$5.4 billion in the first six months since launching. Do you think that's a realistic forecast? And do you
think Spot Ether ETFs would prove to be as popular as Spot Bitcoin ETFs?
Oh, absolutely. I think, first of all, that's probably a relatively conservative estimate.
I don't like to get into forecasts in the very short term. I tend to think more about the sort of super
long term. When we think strategically about the total long term, we see a kind of market for
tokenized Ethereum-based digital assets in kind of the tens of trillions of dollars. And so for Ethereum,
I think that means it's going to be, you know, there could be eventually hundreds of billions just
on that one crypto asset. Over in Bitcoin, we see a close analogy to gold. Bitcoin is now like,
you know, a bit over a trillion. I think about the gold market cap, which is in the range of $14
trillion. And I think those things might be comparable over time. But when I say over time,
I mean like 20 to 30 years of inflows and institutional investment, not six months or 12 months.
B-圈的恐懼贪婪指数現在回到了贪婪.你在上周有加仓嗎?有的在留言區
幫我打個1,沒有的打個2.你看懂了別人恐懼我貪婪的這個規律了嗎?
你又買了哪一種弊呢?歡迎在下面跟大家分享,另外跟大家說個
Telegram上面新的空投小遊戲叫做OKX Racer,遊戲內容超簡單,就是去猜比特幣
5秒內的漲或跌就可以得到相對應的分數。那如果連續猜對呢,還可以得到加倍的積分。
OKX官方已經說了後續會有獎勵退出,這是一個不用成本的魯毛,熱騰騰剛出來的一個小遊戲,
無聊的話可以玩玩看。最後呢,美國5000萬的B圈選民跟你應該都會想要了解一下
美國這次的大選結果會怎麼樣影響B圈?推薦你去看一下這兩集。
謝謝你看到這裡喔,歡迎用下面的連結到LINE跟Discord群組
跟努力的大家一起討論。我們在OKXPN派網呢,跟其他的大交易所
都幫大家爭取到了最高8折20%OFF的交易手續費減免。
用下面的連結註冊呢,你的交易成本就更低了。
也歡迎告訴我你接下來想要看什麼,我們在B圈繼續努力,下次見,掰掰!